[{"answer": "Well it's certainly different being out of power.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Condoleezza Rice, is it more fun being in power or is it more fun after power?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, it's less of what I can do now that I couldn't do then than -- there isn't the sort of relentlessness of the days.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "But in practical reality what can you now do you couldn't do, that you missed?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Well I was going to be a concert pianist.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams that one day you'd be in there?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I'm a mad football --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Because you're a mad football nut, aren't you?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, that was what was extraordinary.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What values did they give you?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "ICE: Well, because there's no greater challenge and there is no greater honor than to be in public service.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "And why would you convince yourself that you had done this terrible, God-forsaken job?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well no, I'm -- I'm pretty far from that.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "You're not far off, are you?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Anything you want to share with me?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, not a sniffle.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Nothing but a sniffle?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "And I --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, you --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "How -- how do you stop getting a cold?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "ICE: You don't get colds.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What are they?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, occasionally.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Keeping fit -- did you drink alcohol when you were in office?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Sure, occasionally.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Did you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "-- can you ever actually get intoxicated?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "I'm still fit.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Are you still absurdly fit?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Because I like to exercise in the morning and I like to have the whole day before me after I exercise.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Why do you do this?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "About an hour.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "How -- how long do you do it for?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I do cardio.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Pump weights?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I do some kick boxing.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Kick boxing?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "I don't think.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Who do you think of when you're smashing the -- the bag?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Hmm.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I have to -- first of all, Birmingham was not an easy place grow up if you were black, but I was fortunate to live in a very loving family, very loving community.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "It must be a great sadness, isn't it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, I think I had -- I have, perhaps part of my father's personality.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Did he make you tough?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, he knew a little bit because he died in 2000.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What would he have made of what happened to you?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well I think she would have been amazed.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "She'd been amazed, do you think?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "My mom was a lady in the nicest sense of the term.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What kind of woman was she?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, the fact is that our politics is pretty rough.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "To use the language of the gun in --in that kind of way?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "-- experienced it myself.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "But should it -- should it be that rough?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Well, let me just say -- all of that said, I would like to see the politics cool down.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What about towards -- what about towards opponents?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, I'm very fond of the president personally.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "How's President Obama doing, do you think?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, I think that he is a fine person and he's doing his best for this country and I was personally quite gratified that America elected a black president.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "But could you have been tempted, do you think, in other circumstances, to vote for President Obama?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "He doesn't need me in his administration.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Would you do it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I don't do hypothetical, Piers.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Hypothetically?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, let me -- let me finish with the --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Would you -- would you join the Tea Party?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Well, there's a long logic chain there.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Because if -- if your party gets split by her and the Tea Party, isn't that a big problem for you?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I -- I have no -- I do international politics.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Could you win with her do you think?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I -- I'm not fearful of the -- the candidates that are on the horizon.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "-- you're not fearful of that candidate being Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Of course you can.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "But you can't ever win a war on terror, can you?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "You can win this war against the extremist who did what they did to us on September 11th.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I do think we're winning the war in Afghanistan, but it's very, very slow.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Are we winning the war in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Well I don't like time tables, to be quite frank.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "I mean, is there not an absolutely obvious problem here, which is the moment you set a time table, the Taliban -- they know their terrain, they disappear, they regroup, they wait?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "There's a lot of corruption in Afghanistan.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Does it worry your, as somebody who in terms of personal probity has never been questioned, a woman of integrity, that you're doing business with President Karzai, who most people would say on the ground is, you know, borderline corrupt?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Of course -- of course.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Would that concern you?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, the same set of circumstances may not lead you to the same set of tools.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How do you choose?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "ICE: Well I think he was certainly a very dangerous man.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "-- Ahmadinejad?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Oh, I would -- I would certainly -- kept -- well first of all, you don't have to make a choice.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "If you were -- if you were still a secretary of state, and Saddam Hussein was still alive, you can't tell me now knowing what we know about all these countries, that you wouldn't be kept awake more by North Korea and Iran than you would by Iraq, would you?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Piers, the fact is that what you know today can affect what you do tomorrow, but not what you did yesterday.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Do you regret now using the weapons of mass destruction as a pretext of war?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, I don't dispute that he didn't have stockpiles of weapons of mass destruction.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "You wouldn't dispute that?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "No, I think the mistake -- and this was a mistake -- was to put a spotlight simply on the weapons of mass destruction.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "-- or would you?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, the reasons for this war, again, were that Saddam Hussein was a threat --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "That he was told to go and do this, and effectively sold the -- the reasons for this war on the evidence which actually turned out to be bogus?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Of course, and it was a reasonable question to ask after 9-11.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "But you're aware that there was a misconception by a number of Americans that Saddam must have been involved in 9-11?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Given the centrality of the Middle East to American security and to the security of the free world, absolutely.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "That is a price worth paying, you think?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Well, actually I live in California now.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "How have you avoided being snared in the marital trap?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "I've come close.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "How close have you come?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I'm not going there.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "How many times?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Do you hold out hope?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Did you dream of a fairy tale wedding?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Well, thank you.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "You're quite a catch; aren't you?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Are you romantic?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Well, I love romantic music and romantic movies and --", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "How does it manifest itself?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Are you -- are you high maintenance?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "You don't know what gumbo is?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "It's -- it's seafood and sausage in a very, very thick sauce.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "Is it meat, fish, or is it?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "Uh, the Stanford Cardinals these days.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "So on this hypothetical date, I've had gumbo and I'd be watching which football team?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "ICE: Yes.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Not all night as well?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "I can imagine that.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 800, "question": "What are you 30?", "qSentId": 799}, {"answer": "We'll leave it at that .", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "Thirty-nine?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "ICE: It's not going to get my juices flowing.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "That's not going to get your juices flowing, is it?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "Compared to Secretary of State.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Playing -- oh, so you consider being a university professor little league; do you?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Playing with Yo-Yo Ma.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "The moment you'd relive again if you got the chance?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110119pmt", "aSentId": 832, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 831}]